weddingvendors.com 2019-06-09

# WeddingVendors.com - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the WeddingVendors.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Credit/Debit Card Information
  * (etc.)

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone number
  * (etc.)

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.weddingvendors.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

### Third-Party Ad Serving

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [NAI](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "Network Advertising Initiative"). 

#### Third-Party: Exponential

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com). 

Exponential creates an anonymous, hashed ID, third-party tracking cookie in your browser from the domain tribalfusion.com that persists for three months, which you can opt out of at their [opt- out](http://exponential.com/privacy/opt-out/) page. 

### Google and User Information

You can obtain information for how Google manages data in its ad products at [this page](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). This includes AdSense and DoubleClick for Publishers, which are both utilized on this website. 

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/). 

Some of our advertising partners, such as Google Adsense, may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use such technology to deliver the advertisements and links that appear on www.weddingvendors.com sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. 

Other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.weddingvendors.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third- party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third- party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.weddingvendors.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

## Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

When placing an order all credit card information is encrypted at all stages from your browser to our systems, and no credit card information is retained on our web servers. 

All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

## How You Can Access or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your registered account. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
